Finding Aid for Vice-President for Development (University of Michigan) records, 1948-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Development Office, 1943-1992
  - Topical File, 1950-1987
    - Historical files
      - "Development Book" by Alan MacCarthy [report of work of Phoenix Continuation Project subcommittee to draft a charter for the proposed development program], January 1952 (Box 16)
      - Michigan Memorial Phoenix Project
        - Final report, 1960 (Box 16)
      - Phoenix Atomic Research Program minutes
        - 1958-1959 (Box 16)
        - 1960 (Box 16)
    - Alphabetical file
      - Activity reports (monthly), 1969-1979 (Box 17)
      - Ad Hoc Committee, 1972 (Box 17)
      - Alumni Center Campaign, 1980-1981; 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Alumni records, 1965-1967 (Box 17)
      - Alumni Solicitation for Student Aid, 1981-1983 (Box 17)
      - Center for Chinese and Center for Japanese Studies: Fundraising Feasibility Study, 1975 (Box 17)
        [See also: East Asian Capital Campaign]
      - Chemistry Campaign Project, 1983 (Box 17)
      - College of Engineering
        - 1948 (Box 17)
          (See: Historical Files--Cooley Memorial Project
        - Capital Campaign Study, 1972 (Box 17)
        - Capital Campaign Report, 1977 (Box 17)
        - Capital Campaign, 1978 (Box 17)
        - Fundraising Study, 1982 (Box 17)
      - Committee on Program Evaluation (COPE), 1974-1979; 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Database (Development Office), 1973-1977; 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Deferred Giving Program, 1969-1984 (Box 17)
      - Department of Ophthalmology Fundraising Study, 1979 (Box 17)
      - Development Costs, 1970-1974 (Box 17)
      - Development Council
        - General (Box 17)
        - Charter (Box 17)
      - Development Study: John Grenzebach and Associates, June 1979; 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Donor Direction Fund, 1972 (Box 17)
      - East Asian Capital Campaign, 1975-1977; 2 folders (Box 17)
        [See also: Center for Chinese and Center for Japanese Studies]
      - East Asian Capital Campaign, 1975-1977; 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Expansion Plan
        - General, 1976-1977 (Box 18)
        - Hewlett Foundation Report, 1976-1979 (Box 18)
      - $55 Million Campaign
        - Administrative records
          - Campaign plan, 1965 (Box 18)
          - Campaign worker evaluations--Metro Detroit Area (Box 18)
          - Capital gifts campaign study--Kersting, Brown and Company, 1963 (Box 18)
          - Committee member kit (Box 18)
          - Cultivation kit (Box 18)
          - Final report and analysis, 1966-1970 (Box 18)
          - Major donors, 1 microfilms (Box 18)
          - National Corporations Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 18)
          - Objectives of $55 Million Campaign, 1964 (Box 18)
          - Planning and implementation documents, 1964-1966 (Box 18)
          - Pocket guide, 1965 (Box 18)
          - Presentations to potential major donors (Box 18)
          - President Hatcher's statements
            - 1964-1966 (Box 18)
            - [press conference], 1967 (Box 18)
          - Printed
            - Brochures, 3 folders (Box 18)
            - The $55 M Bulletin, 1966-1967 (Box 18)
            - The Vital Margin, 1965-1967 (Box 18)
          - Procedures (Box 18)
          - Slide show, 1966 (Box 35)
          - University history, 1964 (Box 18)
          - Victory celebration, 1967 (Box 18)
        - Unit objectives
          - Advanced Management Center (Box 18)
          - Aerospace Engineering (Box 18)
          - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (Box 18)
          - Continuing Education of Women (Box 18)
          - Economics (Box 18)
          - Engineering, 2 folders (Box 18)
          - Faculty Club (Box 19)
          - Fairlane--Dearborn Campus (Box 19)
          - Geography (Box 19)
          - Graduate Library (Box 19)
          - Great Lakes Research (Box 19)
          - Institute for Medicinal Chemistry (Box 19)
          - Institute for Social Research (Box 19)
          - Institute of Science and Technology (Box 19)
          - International Center (Box 19)
          - Law (Box 19)
          - Medical School (Box 19)
          - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 19)
          - Music (Box 19)
          - Natural Resources (Box 19)
          - Naval Architecture (Box 19)
          - Nu Sigma Nu (Box 19)
          - Phoenix Project (Box 19)
          - Telescope (Box 19)
          - Theater (Box 19)
      - Foundation Program Planning, 1974-1976 (Box 19)
      - Foundation Support, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
      - Furstenberg Student Center Campaign, 1972-1974; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Jacobson, Harvey K., 1975 (Box 19)
      - Law School
        - Capital Gift Campaign Feasibility Study, 1972 (Box 19)
        - Development Program, n.d. (Box 19)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1987 (Box 19)
      - Major Gifts Program, 1973-1975; 1978-1979; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Michigan Today, 1977-1983 (Box 19)
      - Martin Luther King Memorial Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
      - McManus Advertising Agency meeting, 1972 (Box 19)
      - Michigan Alumni Fund
        - General, 1955-1969 (Box 19)
        - Board meeting minutes, 1960-1961; 2 folders (Box 19)
        - Board meetings, 1962; 1964-1968; 6 folders (Box 19)
        - Plan for Solicitation, 1956 (Box 19)
        - Review Committee, 1969 (Box 19)
        - Samples of fundraising appeals, 1953-1964; 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Michigan Annual Giving Program
        - Direct Mail Subcommittee, 1973-1975 (Box 20)
        - Michigan Annual Giving Committee minutes, 1970-1984; 14 folders (Box 20)
        - Program analysis, 1980-1982 (Box 20)
        - Program Ideas Subcommittee, 1973-1977 (Box 20)
        - Reports, 1973-1984 (Box 20)
      - Michigan Gift Program, 1967 (Box 20)
      - National Institute for Burn Medicine: Feasibility Study, 1979 (Box 20)
      - Pooled Income Fund, 1971-1979; 2 folders (Box 20)
        [See also: Unitrust]
      - Presidents Club
        - Annual meeting program, 1963-1982 (scattered) (Box 21)
        - Executive committee, 1961-1982; 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Founding (Box 21)
        - Handbook (Box 21)
        - Membership list, 1979 (Box 21)
        - Newsletter, 1981-1983 (Box 21)
        - Recruiting kit, 1984 (Box 21)
        - Speeches, 3 audiocassettes (Box 21)
        - Volunteer program, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
      - Radock, Michael--correspondence, 1965-1981 (Box 21)
      - Replacement Hospital Project, 1979-1980; 3 folders (Box 21)
      - Regents' Communications/Gift Reports
        - 1968-1971, 7 folders (Box 21)
        - 1972-1984, 13 folders (Box 22)
      - Staff meetings
        - Regular, 1969-1975; 3 folders (Box 22)
        - Retreats, 1970-1979; 11 folders (Box 22)
      - Study Committee on School and College Fundraising, 1972 (Box 22)
      - School and College Relations Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 22)
      - Student Awareness Study Committee, 1981 (Box 22)
      - Tappan Society, 1981 (Box 22)
      - Unitrust, 1971-1981; 8 folders (Box 22)
        [See also: Pooled Income Fund]
      - Washington Summer Intern Program, 1972-1974 (Box 22)
  - Photographs and Slides, 1950s-1980s
    Photographs consists of images dating from the 1950s to the 1980s taken primarily for publicity purposes. The photographs document most of the major construction projects on campus since about 1965 and offer unique images of student life. Most have been published.
    - Photo Prints, 1950s-1980s
      - Aerial views
        - Crisler Arena construction (Box 23)
        - Football stadium, November 22, 1969 (Box 23)
        - Hospitals, ca., 1975 (Box 23)
        - North Campus, ca., 1965 (Box 23)
      - Alumni Association (Box 23)
      - Barbour-Waterman demolition (Box 23)
      - Bentley Historical Library courtyard, 1972-1983 (Box 23)
      - Biological Station, Pellston, MI, 1970 (Box 23)
      - Botanical Gardens (Box 23)
      - Buildings--miscellaneous (Box 23)
      - Burn Unit, University of Michigan Hospitals, ca., 1979 (Box 23)
      - Burton Tower (Box 23)
      - Business Administration, School of (Box 23)
      - Campaign for Michigan leaders (Box 23)
      - Chelsea Clinic (Box 23)
      - Chemistry (Box 23)
      - Chrysler Engineering Center (Box 23)
      - Clements Library (Box 23)
      - Commencement
        - 1980 (Box 23)
        - 1983 (Box 23)
        - [Walter Cronkite], 1984 (Box 23)
      - Crisler Arena (Box 23)
      - Dental School, ca., 1973 (Box 23)
      - Development Council board of directors, ca., 1950; 1953 (Box 23)
      - Dormitories (Box 23)
      - Dow Building, 1983 (Box 23)
      - Economics Building and fire, 1981 (Box 23)
      - Engineering, College of (Box 23)
      - Eaton Corporation Gift, 1977 (Box 23)
      - Galens Tag day, ca., 1980 (Box 23)
      - Geology Laboratory (Box 23)
      - Graduate Library--north building and south building construction (Box 23)
      - Great Lakes Research Division, ca., 1980 (Box 23)
      - Haven Hall (Box 23)
      - Highway Safety Research Institute, ca., 1975 (Box 23)
      - Inglis House (Box 23)
      - Institute for Social Research (Box 23)
      - Jackson, Jesse (Box 23)
      - Kellogg Eye Center, 1980-1983 (Box 23)
      - Kelsey Museum (Box 23)
      - Laser Fusion Experiment, ca., 1977 (Box 23)
      - Law Library underground annex construction, 1978 (Box 23)
      - Law Quad (Box 23)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts Building, ca., 1950 (Box 23)
      - Martha Cook Residence Hall (Box 23)
      - Michigan League (Box 23)
      - Michigan Union (Box 23)
      - Microbiology (Box 23)
      - Minorities (Box 23)
      - Minority Summer Program, ca., 1980 (Box 23)
      - Mott, C.S., Hospital (Box 23)
      - Musuem of Art (Alumni Memorial Hall), ca., 1980 (Box 23)
      - Museums (Box 23)
      - Music, School of (Box 23)
      - Music Camp (Interlochen) (Box 23)
      - Natural Resources (Dana Building) (Box 23)
      - Naval Architecture (Box 23)
      - North Campus Commons (Box 23)
      - Nursing, School of (Box 23)
      - Pathology (Box 23)
      - Pharmacy, College of (Box 23)
      - Phoenix Laboratory--Ford Nuclear Reactor (Box 23)
      - Physical therapy (Box 23)
      - Physics-Astronomy Building (Box 23)
      - Plaques, busts, etc (Box 23)
      - Power Center construction (Box 23)
      - Presidents of the University of Michigan (Box 23)
      - Presidents Club (Box 23)
      - President's house (Box 23)
      - Program for Urban/Minority High School Students, ca., 1980 (Box 23)
      - Public Health (Box 23)
      - Rackham Building, 1983 (Box 23)
      - Regents meeting (Box 23)
      - Registration (Box 23)
      - Residential College (East Quad) (Box 23)
      - School of Art masked ball, 1979-1980 (Box 23)
      - Science (Box 23)
      - Simpson (Thomas H.) Memorial Institute (Box 23)
      - Speech (Box 23)
      - Speech Camp (Camp Shady Trails) (Box 23)
      - Stadium--installation of artificial turf (Box 23)
      - Student Activities Building (Box 23)
      - Student scenes, 4 folders (Box 23)
      - Taubman Library entrance, 1983 (Box 23)
      - Towsley Center (Box 23)
      - Television Center (Argus Building) (Box 23)
      - Undergraduate Library (Box 23)
      - University Hospitals (Box 23)
      - Upjohn Pharmacology Center (Box 23)
      - WUOM records collection (Box 23)
      - Yost Arena remodeling (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - Slides, 1950s-1980s
      Slides (6 linear feet) consists of slides taken by News and Information Service photographers from the 1950s to the 1980s. The bulk of the slides, however, date from the 1960s and 1970s. Most of the slides document campus life and the physical plant of the University of Michigan. In addition, there is a small group of slides documenting the Dearborn and Flint campuses of the University and the city of Ann Arbor. Persons represented in "Individuals" include University of Michigan faculty, staff, and administrators, as well as visitors to the campus; slides of Development Office staff members can be found in this category.
      - University of Michigan
        - Aerial views [slide box]
          - Campus (Box 33)
        - Buildings
          - Aerospace Engineering (Box 33)
          - Alumni Center (Box 33)
          - Angell Hall (Box 33)
          - Art and Architecture Building (Box 33)
          - Athletic buildings (Box 33)
          - Bentley Historical Library (Box 33)
          - Buhl Building (Human Genetics) (Box 33)
          - Buhr Building (Box 33)
          - Burton Tower (Box 33)
          - Business Administration (Box 33)
          - Center for Continuing Education for Women (Box 33)
          - Chemistry (Box 33)
          - Clements Library (Box 33)
          - Computing Center (Box 33)
          - Dennison (Physics/Astronomy) (Box 33)
          - Dental School [old and new buildings] (Box 33)
          - Economics Building [and fire] (Box 33)
          - Education (Box 33)
            (see: Miscellaneous)
          - Engineering
            - Central Campus (Box 33)
            - North Campus (Box 33)
          - Fleming Administration Building (Box 33)
          - Ford (Gerald R.) Library (Box 33)
          - Fraternities and sororities
            (includes: Alpha Chi Omega, Alpha Delta Phi, Beta Theta Pi, Delta Gamma, Gamma Phi Beta)
          - Frieze (Box 33)
            [see: Miscellaneous]
          - Graduate Library (Box 33)
          - Haven Hall (Box 33)
          - Health Service (Box 33)
          - Highway Safety Research Institute (Box 33)
          - Hill Auditorium (Box 33)
          - Housing
            (includes: Baits, Barbour, Bursley, Helen Newberry, Northwood, Oxford, Residential College, South Quad, Stockwell, West Quad, and interior scenes)
          - I [Inglis House; Incinerator] (Box 33)
          - Institute for Continuing Legal Education (Box 33)
          - Institute for Social Research (Box 33)
          - Institute of Science and Technology (Box 33)
          - Kellogg Eye Center (Box 34)
          - Kelsey Museum (Box 34)
          - Lane Hall (Box 34)
          - Law Quad (Box 34)
          - Literature, Science and the Arts (Box 34)
          - Little, C.C. (Box 34)
          - Lorch Hall (Box 34)
          - Martha Cook Building (Box 34)
          - Mason Hall (Box 34)
          - Matthaei Botanical Gardens (Box 34)
          - Medical Center
            includes Mott Children's Hospital and old and new hospital buildings)
            - 1960s (Box 34)
            - 1970s (Box 34)
            - 1980s (Box 34)
          - Medical Science Buildings (Box 34)
          - Mendelssohn Theatre (Box 34)
          - Michigan League (Box 34)
          - Michigan Union (Box 34)
          - Modern Languages Building (Box 34)
          - Museum of Art (Box 34)
          - Museums Building (and Museums Annex) (Box 34)
          - Music, School of [old building and Earl V. Moore Building] (Box 34)
            (includes McIntosh Theatre])
          - Natural Resources (Dana) (Box 34)
          - Natural Science (Box 34)
          - News and Information Services (Box 34)
          - North Campus--miscellaneous [includes North Campus Commons] (Box 34)
          - North Hall (Box 34)
          - North University Building (NUB) (Box 34)
          - Nursing, School of (Box 34)
          - Observatory (Box 34)
          - Parking structures (Box 34)
          - Pharmacy (Box 34)
          - Physics, West (Box 34)
          - Power Center (Box 34)
          - President's House (Box 34)
          - Public Health, School of (Box 34)
          - Rackham Building (Box 34)
          - Regents Plaza (Box 34)
          - Simpson Memorial Institute (Box 34)
          - Student Activities Building (Box 34)
          - Student Publications Building (Box 34)
          - Tappan Hall (Box 34)
          - Taubman Medical Library (Box 34)
          - Telecommunications (Box 34)
          - Television Center (Box 34)
          - Trotter House (Box 34)
          - Undergraduate Library (Box 34)
          - University Publications (Box 34)
          - Victor Vaughan (Box 34)
          - WUOM (Box 34)
          - Miscellaneous
            - [Education; Frieze; Health Service; C.C. Little; Lane Hall; Victor Vaughan] (Box 34)
        - Campus scenes
          - General
            - 1960s (Box 34)
            - 1970s (Box 34)
            - 1980s, 2 folders (Box 34)
            - Undated (Box 34)
          - Artwork (mural) at construction site, 1966 (Box 34)
          - Diag (Box 34)
          - Monuments, sculptures, and plaques (Box 34)
          - Regents Plaza and the Cube (Box 34)
        - Classroom scenes
          - 1960s (Box 35)
          - 1970s (Box 35)
          - 1980s (Box 35)
        - Development Office
          - Campaign for Michigan (Box 35)
          - $55 Million Campaign: slide show (Box 35)
          - Miscellaneous [meetings of Annual Funds Coordinating Committee, Faculty Advisory Committee, President's Club, staff; retreat] (Box 35)
        - Events
          - Commencement
            - 1961-1974 (Box 35)
              [slide box: includes 1961-62, 1964-65, 1967, 1972-74]
            - 1976-1987 (Box 35)
              [slide box: includes 1976, 1978-80, 1984, 1987]
            - 1976-1983, 7 folders (Box 35)
            - 1984, 1986-1987; 3 folders (Box 36)
          - Dedication--Center for Afro-American and African Studies, 1971 (Box 36)
          - For (Gerald R.) Library--laying of cornerstone, Jun 19, 1979 (Box 36)
          - Gamelon concert, June 1977 (Box 36)
          - Inauguration of Harold Shapiro, April 14, 1980; 2 folders (Box 36)
          - Japanese Automotive Industry conference, January 14, 1981 (Box 36)
          - May Festival
            - 1968, 1972-1975 (Box 36)
            - 1978-1980, 1983-1984 (Box 36)
          - Medieval Festival, 1981 (Box 36)
          - Messiah, 1977; 1982-1983 (Box 36)
          - Mondale (Walter) rally, October 1984 (Box 36)
          - Pioneer Venus news conference, November 1978 (Box 36)
          - Regents (Board of) meetings
            - 1967-1988 (scattered), 2 folders (Box 36)
            - Passing of gavel from Allan Smith to Harold Shapiro, December 21, 1979 (Box 36)
          - Theater: Gerda Seligson Players: Plautus's Amphitryon, April 1980 (Box 36)
          - University Press Club of Michigan, 1977; undated (Box 36)
        - Individuals
          - A
            - Abdel-Massih, Ernest (Box 36)
              (with Mar Ignatius Zakka, head of Syrian Orthodox Church)
            - Abrams, Floyd (New York Times) (Box 36)
            - Aisen, Cindy Fox (Box 36)
            - Allen, Walter C. (Box 36)
            - Arnheim, Rudolf (Box 36)
          - B
            - Baker, Deane (Box 36)
            - Baker, Gwendolyn (Box 36)
            - Baroway, Malcolm (Box 36)
            - Bates, Marston (Box 36)
            - Bayliss, George (Box 36)
            - Beeman, Alice (Box 36)
            - Berger, Joel (Box 36)
            - Bernstein, Leonard (at Hill Auditorium) (Box 36)
            - Blanchard, Frank (Box 36)
            - Bogdan, Albert (Box 36)
            - Brazer and Shapiro at capitol in Lansing (Box 36)
            - Briggs, Robert (Box 36)
            - Broadnax, Stanley (Box 36)
            - Brodsky, Josif (Box 36)
            - Brown, Robert (Box 36)
            - Buning, Herm (at mural dedication, 1979) (Box 36)
            - Burrows, Ed (Box 36)
          - Beatrix, Queen (Box 36)
          - Blanchard, Governor James (Box 36)
          - C
            - Canady, Alexa (Box 36)
            - Canham, Donald (Box 36)
            - Carter, Richard (Box 36)
            - Cash, William (Box 36)
            - Cavender, George (Box 36)
            - Chandler, David (Box 36)
            - Cobb, Jean (Box 36)
            - Cole, David (Box 36)
            - Collins, Russ (Box 36)
            - Cooper, Constance (Box 36)
            - Crane, Gerald (Box 36)
            - Crockett, George (Box 36)
            - Crockett, Larry (Box 36)
            - Cudlip, William (Box 36)
            - Cutler (Box 36)
          - D
            - Deskins, Donald (Box 36)
            - Dewey, Mary (Box 36)
            - Doerr, Robert (Box 36)
            - Donahue, Thomas (Box 36)
            - Doster, Roger (Box 36)
            - Douvan, Elizabeth (Box 36)
            - Driscoll, James (Box 36)
            - Dumas, Rhetaugh (Box 36)
          - Dalai Lama (Box 36)
          - Duderstadt, James (Box 36)
          - E
            - Edwards, Lamar (Box 36)
            - Edwards, Rosalee (Box 36)
            - Eich, Rich (Box 36)
            - Elgass, Jane (Box 36)
            - Erwin, Robert (Box 36)
            - Evans, Billy (Box 36)
          - F
            - Fonville, Charles (Box 36)
            - Ford, Geraldine Bledsoe (Box 36)
            - Forman, Robert (Box 36)
            - Franks, Julius (Box 36)
            - Freedman, Dave (Box 36)
            - Frieder, Bill (Box 36)
            - Fullerton, Charles (Box 36)
            - Furlong, Harold (Box 36)
          - Fleming, Robben (Box 36)
          - Ford, Gerald R.--visits to campus
            - (September): campaign kickoff, 1976 (Box 36)
            - (December): commencement, 1976 (Box 36)
            - 1977-1979 (Box 37)
            - 1980 (Box 37)
          - G
            - Gallagher, Terry (Box 37)
            - Gameta, George (Box 37)
            - Gardener, Patrick (Box 37)
            - Ginnever, Charles (Box 37)
            - Goebel, Paul (Box 37)
            - Goodall, Leonard (Box 37)
            - Goodwin, Gil (Box 37)
            - Goodwin, William (Box 37)
            - Gordus, Adon (Box 37)
            - Goss, Thomas (Box 37)
            - Graff, Lou (Box 37)
            - Greenquist, Peter (Box 37)
          - H
            - Halperin, Morton (Box 37)
            - Hamilton, John (Box 37)
            - Harbaugh, Jim (Box 37)
            - Harris, James (Box 37)
            - Hesseltine, Douglas (Box 37)
            - Heubner, Gertrude (Box 37)
            - Hibbard, Oliver (Box 37)
            - Hicks, June (Box 37)
            - Hildebrandt, Herbert (Box 37)
            - Hill, Jesse (Box 37)
            - Hindley, Fred (Box 37)
            - Host, Margaret Ayers (Box 37)
            - Howe, Robert (mural dedication, 1979) (Box 37)
          - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 37)
          - J
            - Jacknow, Karen (Box 37)
            - Jackson, Jesse (Box 37)
            - Jacobson, Harvey (Box 37)
            - Johnson, Harold (Box 37)
            - Johnson, Kelly (Box 37)
            - Johnson, Ron (Box 37)
            - Jones, Caroline R (Box 37)
            - Jones, James Earl (Box 37)
            - Jones, John (Box 37)
            - Jones, Rob (Box 37)
          - K
            - Kamisar, Yale (Box 37)
            - Kamrowski, Gerome (with windmill sculpture) (Box 37)
            - Karlstrom, Sten (Box 37)
            - Katz, Lee (Box 37)
            - Kelly, E. Lowell (Box 37)
            - Knapp, Marilyn (Box 37)
            - Knoll, Erwin (Box 37)
            - Konrad, G. (Electron Physics Lab) (Box 37)
            - Koykka, Thomas (Box 37)
          - L
            - Lee, Wono (Box 37)
            - Liebensberger, Jean (Box 37)
            - Lyons, Wendell (Box 37)
          - Lousma, Jack (Box 37)
          - M
            - McCluhan, Marshall (Box 37)
            - McConnell, James (Box 37)
            - McCracken, Paul (Box 37)
            - McCree, Wade (Box 37)
            - MacInnes, Margo (Box 37)
            - McKeachie, Wilbert (Box 37)
            - Markley, John (Box 37)
            - Martel, William (Box 37)
            - Marx, Margaret (Box 37)
            - Mason, Marilyn (Box 37)
            - Materka, Pat (Box 37)
            - Matthaei, Regent Frederick (Box 37)
            - Matthaei, Frederick, Jr (Box 37)
            - Mauk, Fred (Box 37)